{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Blind and Shade Cleaning Services","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","__cache./api/resource/task/40182/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40182,"taskName":"Blinds or Shades - Clean","taskDescription":"Clean or Treat Blinds or Shades","xmTaskDescriptor":"Blind and Shade Cleaning Services","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":274,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Blinds Shades cleaning Clean custom","textMessagingName":"Cln Blinds","rolloverLongDesc":"Generally done in the home. May include application of fabric protection sprays like Scotchguard.","rolloverShortDesc":"Clean blinds \u0026 shades in the home.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Clean or Treat Blinds or Shades.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Blind \u0026 Shade Cleaning Services \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":13,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":5,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Clean Blinds or Shades","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Blinds or Shades - Clean","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Blind and Shade Cleaning Project","urlName":"Blinds-or-Shades-Clean","taskConsiderationId":1,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Blind Cleaning Services - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | HomeAdvisor","searchKeywords":"Blinds, Shades, cleaning, Clean, custom, horizontal, treat, maid, cleaners, cleaner, treatment, covering, window, vertical, mini, drapes, venetian, wash","emcCategoryOid":-12014,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":491,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true,"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40182/":{"taskOID":40182,"originalTaskOID":40182,"setID":491,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":5081,"questionDisplayText":"Type of Cleaning","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of cleaning do you need? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":2775,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Requires cleaning/maintenance","answerDisplayText":"Requires cleaning/maintenance","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6006,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Stain removal","answerDisplayText":"Stain removal","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4662,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Pet stains","answerDisplayText":"Pet stains","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2120,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Dust","answerDisplayText":"Dust","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1937,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Dirt/grime","answerDisplayText":"Dirt/grime","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3843,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Mildew","answerDisplayText":"Mildew","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5082,"questionDisplayText":"Type of Blinds","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Which of the following kinds of blinds need cleaning? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":3081,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Horizontal vinyl/metal mini-blinds","answerDisplayText":"Horizontal vinyl/metal mini-blinds","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3082,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Horizontal wood/wood-like blinds","answerDisplayText":"Horizontal wood/wood-like blinds","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6719,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Vinyl/metal vertical blinds","answerDisplayText":"Vinyl/metal vertical blinds","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7102,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Wood/wood-like vertical blinds","answerDisplayText":"Wood/wood-like vertical blinds","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2362,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Fabric vertical blinds","answerDisplayText":"Fabric vertical blinds","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5384,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Roller shades","answerDisplayText":"Roller shades","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7132,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Woven wood shades","answerDisplayText":"Woven wood shades","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":5081,"questionDisplayText":"Type of Cleaning","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of cleaning do you need? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":2775,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Requires cleaning/maintenance","answerDisplayText":"Requires cleaning/maintenance","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6006,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Stain removal","answerDisplayText":"Stain removal","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4662,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Pet stains","answerDisplayText":"Pet stains","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2120,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Dust","answerDisplayText":"Dust","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1937,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Dirt/grime","answerDisplayText":"Dirt/grime","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3843,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Mildew","answerDisplayText":"Mildew","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":2775,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Requires cleaning/maintenance","answerDisplayText":"Requires cleaning/maintenance","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6006,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Stain removal","answerDisplayText":"Stain removal","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4662,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Pet stains","answerDisplayText":"Pet stains","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2120,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Dust","answerDisplayText":"Dust","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1937,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Dirt/grime","answerDisplayText":"Dirt/grime","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3843,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Mildew","answerDisplayText":"Mildew","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5082,"questionDisplayText":"Type of Blinds","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Which of the following kinds of blinds need cleaning? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":3081,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Horizontal vinyl/metal mini-blinds","answerDisplayText":"Horizontal vinyl/metal mini-blinds","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3082,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Horizontal wood/wood-like blinds","answerDisplayText":"Horizontal wood/wood-like blinds","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6719,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Vinyl/metal vertical blinds","answerDisplayText":"Vinyl/metal vertical blinds","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7102,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Wood/wood-like vertical blinds","answerDisplayText":"Wood/wood-like vertical blinds","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2362,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Fabric vertical blinds","answerDisplayText":"Fabric vertical blinds","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5384,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Roller shades","answerDisplayText":"Roller shades","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7132,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Woven wood shades","answerDisplayText":"Woven wood shades","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":3081,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Horizontal vinyl/metal mini-blinds","answerDisplayText":"Horizontal vinyl/metal mini-blinds","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3082,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Horizontal wood/wood-like blinds","answerDisplayText":"Horizontal wood/wood-like blinds","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6719,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Vinyl/metal vertical blinds","answerDisplayText":"Vinyl/metal vertical blinds","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7102,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Wood/wood-like vertical blinds","answerDisplayText":"Wood/wood-like vertical blinds","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2362,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Fabric vertical blinds","answerDisplayText":"Fabric vertical blinds","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5384,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Roller shades","answerDisplayText":"Roller shades","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7132,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Woven wood shades","answerDisplayText":"Woven wood shades","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]}]}}